ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Communications Department Photographs
1909-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/176 P
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection contains photographs used by the Communications Department of the ILGWU. Included are photographs documenting ILGWU events and organizations, including conventions and other meetings, strikes and rallies, and local unions and regional departments. Also included are photographs of ILGWU presidents and other officers, political figures, and prominent labor unionists.
7128163
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 25, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 26, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
The precursor to the ILGWU's Communications Department was the Publications and Publicity Department. Though the name and scope of the department changed over time, its primary function stayed the same throughout the history of the ILGWU. The department was responsible for the publication of the ILGWU's official publication Justice, as well as the official editions in Yiddish (Gerechtigkeit), Italian (Giustizia), and Spanish (Justicia), and it was also responsible for cooperating with journalists outside of the union on pieces about the ILGWU. Beyond coordinating such efforts of journalists, the Communications Department provided information about the union to other labor organizations, students, and teachers.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Communications Department consist entirely of subject and biographical files, with related photographs. Taken together, these records document ILGWU events, organizations, and leaders, as well as political figures and other prominent labor unionists.
The Communications Department's alphabetical subject files (5780/176) contain clippings from publications that appear to be produced through the Communications Department or with its cooperation. The clippings in this collection provide concise, published accounts of events and affiliates of the ILGWU, as well as of issues of special interest to the union. The related photograph collection (5780/176 P) includes a variety of images documenting the work of the union, arranged in two series: Events and Organizations, and Personalities. These photographs include large groups of people at meetings, protests, and other events, and ILGWU members, staff, and leaders at work.
The Communications Department's biographical files (5780/177) are of interest not only because they provide sometimes difficult-to-find, basic information on ILGWU members and officers, but because that information was provided by the individuals themselves, on forms provided by the union and designed to be returned to the office when completed. These biographical forms appear to have begun as a project of the editors of Justice, and the information contained includes date and place of birth, when the subject arrived in the United States, positions held in the ILGWU or other unions, and outside activities and interests. The related photograph collection (5780/177 P) includes portraits of some of the individuals represented in the biographical files, as well as photographs of events and miscellaneous photographs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/176: ILGWU Communications Department Records 5780/177: ILGWU Communications Department Biography Files 5780/177 P: ILGWU Communications Department Biography File Photographs
Women's clothing industry -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs; Women's clothing industry -- United States -- Photographs; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- Photographs; Clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs; Clothing workers -- United States -- Photographs; Textile workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs; Textile workers -- United States -- Photographs; Industrial relations -- New York (State) -- Photographs; Industrial relations -- United States -- Photographs; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union -- Photographs; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Communications Dept. -- Photographs
7128163
- AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes: Lane Kirkland and Lech Walesa; ILG Chorus at convention, n.d.; Edward James Olmos "Union Yes", 1989; Kirkland with Yvonne Patz and Bob Hostetter at the Penn State Labor Advisory Committee, 1987; Louise Hildebrand interviews Pa. State Senator Frank O'Connell for an 'America Works' episode, 1987; Cosby Show's Sabrina LeBeauf, 1987; Label for a "Buy American" campaign, 1986
- Alcoholism Project: Alcoholism (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Includes: Picture of man with a bottle of liquor; Article describing AA meetings, 1987
- Alcoholism Project: APALA (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Includes: APALA's second convention, Los Angeles, with Jesse Jackson Jr., David K Trask, Jr., Yuri Kockiyama, Fred T. Korematsu, Rev. Jesse Jackson, Frank Antonio and Kent Wong; APALA march in Washington D.C. with Pres. Kirkland and ILG Pres. Jay Mazur, May 1992; APALA convention, Washington D.C., 1992; APALA march, Los Angeles, n.d.; ILGWU Organizer Francisco Chang at APALA conference, 1993; APALA convention, Washington D.C. with Mazur, 1992
- Archives (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Includes: Graphic for "Dressmakers' General Strike Declared", 1933
- Associate ILGWU Membership: AIM (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Includes: AIM member, Bonnie Kuhns; Jay Mazur at AIM annual executive board meeting, New York, includes Rhonda Sullivan, Dir. Judith Wineman, Nancy Wiles, Marisol Ortiz, AIM Dir. Martin Berger, Fanny Yuen, Ida Yuen, Amadis Prada, 1994; Amira Barros and Rudolfo Guzman display the new chapter banner, 1994; AIM members Houston, Texas, 1994; Kentucky Congressman Tom Barlow with AIM members, Princeton, KT, 1994; AIM convention with Mazur and Director Martin Berger, 1993; AIM Canadian chapter, 1992, ILG headquarters, Toronto, 1992; Director Berger, 1991; AIM Chapter #4 Pres. Thelma Tibbs and members of Local 410, 1992; Mary Jones, AIM chapter Vice President, Bob Sleiger, Ruby Cutts, Congressman Kostmayer, Norma Terry and Mary Berger, 1992; AIM march, New York City, 1992; Executive Vice Pres. Edgar Romney, 1992 in New York City; Vice Pres. Sal Giardina AIM charter, Barbara Truex and Berger, 1989; Officers of the Matawan AIM Chapter, Diana Brody, Barbara Truex, Mary Ann Kammann and Patt Engel, 1990; Associate ILGWU Members (AIM) march, Colorado, 1990; Kentucky AIM Chapter, n.d.; Twenty-Three members for chapter 8 receiving their certificates from Cornell University (ILR), New York, 1991; AIM members celebrate a decision by NLRB, Pa., 1991; AIM members at Camp Solidarity, n.d.; New AIM chapter The Chinese Voice of New York City, 1992; AIM parade float, n.d.; Martin Berger, May 1987; Giardina, April 1987; Berger explains new associate member program to GAC members, 1987; Nancy Manieri, 8-year ILG member, 1989; ILG member, Mary Stephen, n.d.; ILG member Kate Dewald, n.d.; Carol Hine, Jan. 1989; Mazur, Gonzalez and Berger handing out associate membership cards, 1988; AIM members, Colorado, 1989; Berger and Local 543 Pres, Doris Blount greeting the first member of AIM in Ohio, Linda Clark, 1988
- Benefit Funds (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Includes: Clarence Judge, cutter, 1994; Lily Lee, operator, 1994; Frank Lampasi, tailor, 1994; Theresa Borromea, union member, 1994; ILGWU Health Service Plan graphic, 1988; graphic for benefit funds, 1988; Dir. Theodore Bernstein, testifies on catastrophic health insurance, 1987
- Fashion Show (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Includes: Fashion show for Democratic delegates, 1992
- Campaign for Justice (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Includes: Workers strike against four garment companies, El Paso, TX., 1991; Rally for Doomsday strikers in Brooklyn, NY, 1990; Justice Center inauguration, NY, 1994; Doomsday worker return to plant, 1991; Bob Jordan at Headquarters of Brooklyn's Campaign for Justice, 1990; David Dinkins at ILGWU rally, NY, n.d.; Workers celebrate "union representation", 1993; Isratex workers celebrate union election, 1993; ILGWU member celebrates "back pay" check, Brooklyn, NY, 1993; Former member at Domsey, 1991; Domsey plant seized because so safety violations, 1991; ILGWU members hand out pamphlets in NY, 1990; Campaign for Justice booklet, 1990; ILGWU rally, 1990; Domsey Trading workers strike, Brooklyn, NY, 1990; Article on reinstated worker at Mademoiselle Knitwear; Congressman Major Owens speaking at ILGWU rally, 1990; Rev. Jesse Jackson and Jay Mazur at Domsey rally, 1990; Domsey workers on strike, 1990; Giles Robinson at ILGWU rally, 1990
- Canada (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Includes: ILGWU on strike against A. Richman & Sons, 1986; Pres. Jay Mazur with Fernard Daoust secretary general of the Quebec Federation of Labor and Vice. Pres. Gerald Roy, Montreal, 1987; Health and Safety Conference, Toronto, 1988; Members of the Fil D'Or Retiree Club, Montreal, Quebec, 1990; Canadian ILGers protest, Montreal, 1990; Simmons employees protest; 1991; Barbara Cameron of TARP, 1991; Mary Said, President of the Ontario District Council, n.d.; Sam Fichtembaum, V.P. of the district council, 1991; Maria Kucil, district council member, 1991; A.D. of Organizing Tom Steers, 1991; Mannie Bricks, president of the Ontario District Council, 1990; Joseph Danahy and Marlene Hill, co-manager of the Western Canadian Region at the Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1986; Herman Stewart, Toronto manager and Fichtenbaum, 1986; Signing new contract in Toronto, includes V.P. William Villano and Stewart; 1986; Vancouver manager Marlene Hill, 1986; Villano and Chris Kuzik of the Toronto Dress and Sportswear Mfrs. Guild, 1986; ILGWU members march, Toronto, 1987; ILGers rally in Ottawa, 1986; ILGers demonstrate in response to Tiananmen massacre, NY, 1989; Union demonstration, Winnipeg, 1987
- Cartoons & Illustrations (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Includes: Cartoon, "arguing economics with Arnold" by Carol Simpson, 1995; Cartoon, "guarding against skin cancer", by Boileau Rothco Syndication, 1990; Cartoon boycott of Plymouth Rubber Co., 1990; Cartoon boycott of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Co., 1990; Cartoon boycott of John Morrell & Co., 1990; Cartoon boycott of Eastern Airlines, Continental or Aeromexico, 1990; Cartoon boycott of International Paper, 1990; Cartoon boycott of Clark Grave Vault Co., 1990; Business humor by Carol Simpson, 1986; Cartoon boycott of Kawasaki and Shell, 1990; Cartoon "Money and Dress Code" by Sam, 1990; Warehouse humor by Sam, 1990; Job skills humor, 1990; Medicare humor by Ensleman; Hospital costs humor by Carol Simpson; George Bush humor by Kirk, 1989; Medicare humor by Carol Simpson, 1988; Unemployment humor, 1988; Poor working conditions humor by Konopacki, 1988; Ronald Reagan humor by Carol Simpson; 1987; Cartoon for Women Workers; History, 1987; Robert Bork humor by Liederman, 1987; Quit Smoking cartoon, 1987; Anti-Management humor by Huck Konopacki, 1987; Anti-Management humor by Carol Simpson, 1987
- Central States (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Includes: Flood of 1993; Rainfair strikers at rally, 1991; Strikers at DCB in El Paso, Texas, 1991; B.A. Grady May & Chairperson Peggy Wood, 1993; Union workers at Aberdeen Mfg., 1995; Southwest Cupid sign, 1993
- Central States (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Includes: Local 371 members for the Flood Relief Fund, 1993; Labor Day parade with ILGWU banner, St. Louis, MO., 1993; Flood of '93 in Illinois; Flood of '93, Missouri; Flood of 93', Washington, MO.; Workers of Wondermaid, 1993; Workers of Miss Elaine, 1993; Red Cross volunteers in MO., 1993; Members of Local 372, Sunnyvale, TX., 1993; Vice Pres. Paul Winslow, 1993; Texas ILGers with banner, 1993; ILGers at rally, Los Angeles, CA., 1993; Texas ILGers at Martin Luther King Parade, Dallas, 1993; Texas ILGers rally against George Bush, 1992; ILGWU local 593 march, DuQuoin, ILL., 1991; Strikers at Apparel Conditioners Corp., 1992; Workers in Dallas, TX.; 1991; Southwestern Illinois Labor Council, 1992; ILGers of Local 388 at rally in Bowling Green, MO., 1991; ILGers of Local 372; Picture of St. Louis, MO., 1990; Women strikers at Forest City Mfg., circa 1933; Violence at a 1933 strike in St. Louis, 1990; Illinois State Comptroller Roland Burris in White Hall, III., 1986; Local 114 strike, Kansas City, MO.; 1982, Local 525 strike at Helena Sportswear, West Helena, AK., 1989; Paul Winslow and Negotiating Committee, Bridal Originals, Inc. Local 542 from Barad & Co. festival, Salem, MO., 1986; Cloak and Suit Local 114, Kansas City, MO., 1988; Workers from Greene County Mfg. on strike, White Hall, III, 1988; V.P. Winslow, Missouri State Senator Jay Nixon, 1988; Workers at Wentzville Mfg. Co on strike, Wentzville, MO., 1988; Winslow presents plaque, 1988; Paluzi Enterprises, Inc. & Local 360 reach agreement, 1986; Picketing at Greene County Mfg., White Hall, III., 1988; Texas ILGers and other unionists at parade with banner, Arlington, TX., 1993
- Christmas Activities (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Includes: ILGWU chorus at NYC's Bellevue Hospital, 1987
- March on Washington (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Includes: ILGWU Workers' Center in NY at march, 1993; March on Washington for jobs and freedom, 1963; March on Washington, 1993; Woman reads newspaper about March on Washington, 1963; Members of Local 15-088 of Philadelphia at 1993 March in Washington; Local 155 member at march; Bergen-Hudson District members at March; Member of Local 239 in Baltimore at march
- Bill Clinton 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Includes: Pres. Mazur & Bill Clinton, 1992; Bill & Hillary Clinton's Inauguration, 1993; President Clinton and Hillary at MTV Inaugural Ball, 1993; Clinton at National Italian American Foundation conference, n.d.; PA. ILGers voting for 92' election; Members of NY Local 62-32 at torchlight parade for Clinton, 1992; Workers rally for Clinton, 1992; Leafleting in NY's Chinatown, 1992; Festival in Lebanon, KY. for Clinton, 1992; Tipper Gore on campaign trail in NY, 1992; Clinton rally, 1992; Members of Local 187 in Racine, WI., 1992; Clinton & Al Gore at East St. Louis rally, 1992; Clinton with members of Local 183 in St. Louis, 1992; Pres. Jay Mazur, V.P. Ron Alman and Nicholas Bonanno of MA. And GE. Delegations, respectively, 1992; New England delegates 1992 National Convention; Pres. Mazur at Summer stage registration drive, 1992; Bill Clinton at rally in Harrisburg, PA., 1992; Clinton & Gore during '92 campaign; Clinton shaking hands with President John F. Kennedy, 1963; Bill Clinton in Hope, AK., at age 5, 1951; Clinton with saxophone at age 12 in Hot Springs, AK, 1958; Gov. Clinton in Little Rock, AK., 1983; Clinton campaigning for Congress in AK, 1974
- Coalition of Labor Unions: Workers Union (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Includes: The ILGWU contingent at 1993 Coalition of Labor Union Women CLUW convention, Las Vegas, NV.;CLUW convention in Pittsburgh, PA., 1992; Jay Mazur becomes member of CLUW, 1987; Mazur at CLUW convention in Seattle, Washington, n.d.
- Contract Negotiations: Leslie Fay (Box 2, Folder 3)
  includes: The HomeGoods negotiating committee, 1995; ILGWU members who work for Leslie Fay rally in NY, 1994; Nelly Williams, 1995; Pres. Mazur and V.P. Sol Hoffman, Northeast Director at rally in NY, 1993; PA ILGers protest at Leslie Fay headquarters in NY, 1993; Rally in Greenwich, CT., 1994; Workers in Kingston, Pa. Rally against Leslie Fay, 1994; ILGers protest in NY against Leslie Fay, 1994
- Contract Negotiations (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Includes: Working Mothers March in NY, n.d.; Workers from Atlantic Apparel in PA, vote, 1994; ILGers march in NY, 1994; Strikers in Morrow, GA, 1994; Local 10 Administrator Ron Alman, 1994; Jay Mazur at meeting in Allentown, PA.,1994; Announcing settlement at Dress Joint Council meeting, 1991; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney negotiating with N.Y. Skirt & Sportswear Assoc., 1991; Mazur addresses Dress Joint Council, 1991; Various union members in NY & NJ, 1991
- Contract Negotiations (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Includes: Various union members in NY & NJ, 1991; V.P. Samuel Byer, 1991; Pres. Mazur, Executive V.P. Romney and V.P. Ronald Alman in New England, 1991; Labor songs are sung, 1991; V.P. Joseph Fisher, 1982; President Sol Chaikin and ZENSEN Pres. Tadanobu Usami, 1981; Fisher, Eastern D.C. contract manager, n.d., Pres. Mazur and V.P. Alman in New England, 1988; Knitgoods ILGers with Local 155 manager Local Lewis and Local Pres. Murry Hendler, 1988
- Contract Negotiations (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Includes: Pres. Mazur and V.P. Sam Byer during negotiations, 1988; V.P. Romney opens sportswear negotiations, 1988; Members of Northeast Dept., 1988; Meeting held in East PA region, 1989; Workers at Model Garment, Frackville, PA., 1988; Manager Norman Lewis in negotiations with United Knitwear Manufacturers League, 1988; Manager Irving Bakal and Sheldon Edelman during negotiations, 1988; Truckers from NY Local 102, 1988; ILGers sign up voters in NY, 1988
- Convention, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Includes: Ohio delegates work on convention resolution, n.d.; Eastern Shore Area Council at Convention; Local 601 at convention; Local 185 at convention; Local 62-32 at convention; New England Region at convention; Executive V.P. Romney, 1989; Lee, manager of 132-98-102, second largest local in the ILG; Nutter, created immigrant assistant program for L.A. County Federation of Labor, 1989; Local 106 at convention
- Convention, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Includes - Senator Al Gore (D-Tenn.) at convention; NY Governor, Mario Cuomo at convention; Desmond Sampson, general secretary, Garment & Allied Workers' Union (GAWU) of South Africa at convention; Neil Kearney, secretary, International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF) at convention; Nancy Riche, exec. V.P., Canadian Labour Congress at convention; Art Rodriguez, V.P. United Farm Workers at convention; Actor Edward James Olmos at convention; Jack Sheinkman, president Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union at convention; Marion Wright Edelman, dir., Children's Defense Fund at convention; Norman Hill, civil rights leader, president A. Philip Randolph Institute
- Convention, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Includes: Vermont Governor Madeleine Kunin, 1986; Sol Chaikin & Jay Mazur, n.d.; Executive V.P. Irwin Solomon, 1986; Shirley Carr, president of the Canadian Labour Congress, 1986; Pres Chaikin announces retirement, 1986
- Convention, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Includes: President Sol Chaikin; ILGWU Chorus; General Secretary Treasurer Jay Mazur; Exec. V.P. Romney, 1986; Barbara Laufman, NYS District Asst. Director, 1986; Gerald Roy, Canadian Director, 1986; Paul Winslow, Central States director, 1986; Lane Kirkland, president of the AFL-CIO, 1986; Union members from Cleveland, 1986; South Carolina's Sen. Ernest "Fritz" Hollings, 1986
- Convention, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1a)
  Includes Pictures from convention, ILGers, continued
- Convention, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Includes: Exec. V.P. Romney, New Jersey, 1994; V.P. Sal Giardina, New Jersey, 1994; V.P. Laufman, 1994
- Convention, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Includes: First Associate ILGWU Membership (AIM) Convention, 1992; Geraldine Willey, President of Local 215 of Willey, CA, 1992; Delegate Debbie Harvin, Local 85, NJ, 1992; Senator Edward Kennedy, 1992; Strikers at Coral Street plants, Miami; 1992; Pres. Mazur, AIM Director Marty Berger, AIM Chapter #3 Pres. Rhonda Sullivan, #3 Exec. Board Member Bertha Brennan, AIM National Pres. Catherine Dewald, 1992; Gerald Roy, 1992; ILGWU logo; NAACP's Benjamin Hooks, 1992; Jose Ramirez, general secretary of FITTVCC/ORI, 1992; Neil Kearney, general secretary of the Industrial Textile Garment and Leather workers Federation (ITGLWF), 1992; Local 10 Manager Israel Mechlowitz, 1992; AFL-CIO Secretary Treasurer Tom Donahue, 1992; General Sec'y-Treas. Irwin Solomon, Exec. V.P. Romney, Jay Mazur, 1992; Hillary Clinton, Mazur, Solomon, 1992; Bill Clinton, 1992; Hillary Clinton, 1992
- Cutting Edge (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Includes Cutting Edge Center Spreads, "Spring Flings", 1994; Monica Minguez, sales representative at Et Al, 1994; Sample maker Ruby Salazar, 1994; Grace Raghubir, 1994; Juanita Soto from Et Al, 1994; Carine Dure, Pat Molluso of Et Al, 1994; Variety of hat and flower pictures
- Daycare Centers (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Includes - Vice Pres. Edgar Romney at event for Garment Industry Day Care, NY, 1993; The Chung Pak Daycare Center in NYC, n.d.; Mee-Ling Chin, director of Garment Industry Day Care Center, V.P. Romney, Harold Siegal and Dobbie Flowers, NY, 1988; Youngsters at NYC's Chinatown Day Care Center, 1991; Youngsters at Fashion District Day Care Center in Toronto, 1991; Michael Dukakis, 1988; Youngsters at Fabrican's day care center, 1990; Thanksgiving at Chinatown Day Care, for members of Local 23-25, 1987; Fashion show at Chinatown Day Care of members of Local 23-25, 1987; Kitty Dukakis at Garment Industry Day Care Center, NY, 1988
- Daisy (Box 3, Folder 5a)
  Includes Examining finished garments; fabric review; company logo; garment boxes ready to ship; loading dock; ca. 1980
- Dukakis, Michael (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Convention for Democratic candidate Michael Dukakis, 1988; Michael and Kitty Dukakis, 1988; Dukakis, 1988
- Eastern PA. 1990s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Includes ILGers at Rodney Yetter Sportswear, 1992; Workers of Scotty Fashions, 1994; B.A. Don Kuhns, president of the credit union along with Allentown credit union honorees, 1993; Len Kidd, Phyllis Webb, Western Canadian regional director and V.P. Gerald Roy, Canadian director, 1993; Super Bowl contest winner Tom O'Donnell, 1995; Workers at A & H Sportswear in Easton, PA.; 1994, "Philly Phanatic" with ILG kids at fundraiser for Lou Gehrig's Disease, 1993; Workers protest against employer Louis Clark Co., 1993; 50 year anniversary for Local 111 ILGer, Allentown, PA. 1991; The Liberty Bell; Philadelphia's Historical District; ILG main headquarters in Philadelphia; ILGers from the Chessler Co., n.d.; Workers at Nipon, n.d.; Local 218 member in Miss Teen Pa. Pageant; United States Post Office in Philadelphia, n.d.